It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series.
This is Anmori-Waka by Inoue and Omine.
And yes, it is Muraho series of Utsuka.
Best regards.
Yay!
You guys are good friends.
Yes, we are good friends.
I'm glad.
I've been looking forward to it since yesterday.
Oh, really?
I was really looking forward to it too.
It's called this dialogue series,
What do we have in common?
We have a lot in common.
Yes, we have a lot in common.
Really?
First of all, I was born in October 2002.
That's right.
We are the same.
I can feel it from there, can't I?
I can feel it.
So, Utsuka, Inoue, and Omine formed the group in 2015.
So, you are the initial members.
That's right.
We did a lot of live performances and discussions together from the beginning.
We also did a lot of sports events.
We had athletic meets and so on.
It was difficult.
That was in Sendai, at LaLaLa Hall, wasn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I miss it.
You know what I look like without makeup.
A lot.
I know it.
It's called old red.It's called old red.
Because you're all pretty, too.
Everyone is, too.
You grew up, there.
I was an adult.
Like 8 years ago, right?
That's great.
That's amazing.
Time flies.
It's so fast.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you very much.
The first time I met you was when I observed a live performance of Ebichu.
I met him for the first time when I observed his live at Saitama Super Arena,
I said hello to him at Sakuraebi.
And we started a group together, so we are like rivals,
We were like rivals.
We were the first rival group.
We were like rivals at the beginning.
We had a song.
Sakuraebi, Uka, and Tohoku-san had a rival song.
It was like they were fighting each other.
The lyrics were like, "Friendship and love are not acceptable.
It brings back memories.
The music video, too.
Yes, it was nostalgic.
The voice of the manager is also in the music video.
It's like the managers don't get along with each other.
It was like that,
But on the third day, it was like that,
In fact, all the members were really close,
They came to have dinner together.
They were very friendly with me.
Actually, we are good friends, but we don't say we are bickering now, right?
I haven't. I haven't said anything. I haven't said anything.I didn't say it. I didn't say anything.
Like, "Where did you go?
We're about as close as you can get.
We also like the same artists.
We listen to the same music.
We also like the same songs.
Whenever I post a song on my insta-story or something,
Whenever I post a song on my Instagram story, he always responds.
It's like we listen to the same songs.
I see. There are a lot of them.
Which artist?
Sekawa-san, right?
And Mise.
What?
Yes, that's right. Are they a lot of bands?
I liked bands a lot.
Let's go to Love.
Let's go.
It's one of the promises I want her to make in secret.
If it's anime, it's One Piece.
Yeah.
Is it bad now?
It's bad.
Next August...
Luffy is coming! Like...
Is it the end?
It'll go on for about 2 more years.
Yes, of course.
There are spoilers.
I can't say much here.
My fan also likes One Piece.
He said he's reading the comic books.
than the current anime.
He said he's reading a story that's a year ahead of the current anime.
He said it's very interesting.I hear it's very interesting.
Eh? Geez.
I can't help but look forward to it.
We will continue to share information.
We have a lot of hobbies together.
Lots and lots of things. We also like to exercise.
We have a lot of things in common.
I hope we can deepen our relationship through this project.
I hope we can get to know each other better.
Seino!
Young Yasumori and
and Liz Murahoshi
Special Talk Festival!
Not a staff ride festival
What kind of project is it?
This
What kind of event is this?
This is Yakan-kun, a familiar face.
Hello.
Inside this kettle
there is a paper with a theme.
You pull it out one by one.
and discuss the theme written on the paper.
Let's talk about it together
and come up with an answer.
The plan is to come up with a single answer.
Great, it has a theme.
Then, let's get started.
Let's go ahead and do it.
Then you can draw.
Are you drawing one? Here.
Yes, I'm drawing one.
Okay, here we go.
There you go.Jang.
What are some of the things that happen in a company on the move?
Is it a certain thing in the company on the move?
Expedition? In Tokyo.
Expedition? Do you ever go to the countryside when you are active in Tokyo?
Recently, I went to Okinawa in July.
Hey, I've been looking at your sign-in list.
I saw your sign-in list,
I was looking at everyone's sign-in list, and I was like, "I love Okinawa.
It was your first time as Uka.
Yes, we went there for two days for a two-man show,
And then we moved to Yamanakako.
In the company on the way. I wonder.
After the Okinawa concert,
I went to the airport, came back to Haneda Airport, and took a bus to Yamanakako.
So you just went on the bus.
So, I don't know. So I don't know.
The bus was quite large,
One person, one seat.
Like a handful of seats.
Sometimes I sit in a seat,
What do they do? Basically, I'm looking at my cell phone,
I don't think there is a lot of talking.
It depends on each member.
Most of them are sleeping.
I see. That's right.
And they are all on a very tight schedule,
And sleeping hours, too, you know.
How about Tohoku?
You are in a rural area, so you have to go on a lot of expeditions.
That's right. Like today.
This time, we all drove from Tokyo.
Really?
It's like going to Tokyo from the ship,
Sometimes we take the bullet train, but when we drive,
I wonder if there are people who talk, people who listen to music, and people who sleep.I wonder what it's like...everyone is in the talking group, the music listening group, and the sleeping group.
Oh, they're divided.
Yes, yes, yes.
I get drunk easily, so I'm in charge of the passenger seat,
But when you're a passenger, you have to do a lot of research on the road and so on,
You're a lot of helpers.
Yes, yes, yes. I'm really like a passenger.
That's great.
Like that,
Like, "This way, this way.
Yes, yes, yes.
When the road was a little rough, he would give directions,
Or, "We're almost there.
Do you also make phone calls?
Yes, I do everything.
I'm like a manager.
But before, we used to play werewolf all the time.
Oh, I'm...
I get drunk easily.
We'd all be on our phones,
I guess it's like we're chatting all the time.
That's true. We were like that in the beginning, too,
When you move your seat on the Shinkansen, the seats rotate, right?
So we played UNO there.
We got along well.
We played UNO many times.
That's nice.
That's good.
I see.
They did.
UNO... It's tough to play UNO in a Hiace, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I can't do it.
I was afraid that if I slammed the card, it would roll up into a ball.
After all, what's the point?After all, what is there to say?
Yes, there is such a thing as being in a moving car.
I wonder.
I don't know.
But really now, you know, I was still a little kid then, right? We were in junior high and high school.
We were having fun at that time, but as we get older and the sounds become more and more alike, we tend to break up with each other.
I've certainly heard of breakups,
Some talk, some listen to music, and some sleep.
That's right. They break up.
To each his own.
Ah, let's do that then.
That's just the way it is.
If there is such a thing as being in a moving car, it is each to his own.
Here we go. Ready.
There are some things that happen in a moving car.
Each in his or her own way. It's really important to spend time in different ways.
It's important.
It's time off. It's time for traveling, for work, and so on.
That's right.
Then let's go to the next one.
Next time, I'll be next. You want me to go next?
Then, yes, please.
I'm going.
Then!
Oh! Speaking of exciting catering, I'll have you know that I'm talking about...
Oh! Catering! This is great, isn't it, catering?
I appreciate it.
It's delicious!
What is it really?
Hmmm. I wonder.
Like last year, when I attended Ebichu-san's Akita Bunko,
Um, what do you call it?
Cutting collateral!
Cut collateral!
There was a part where we were making soup with cut collateral,
I was so excited.That really got me excited.
I was really excited.
I mean, Myu, the same member, Digitally Myu,
What was it, 20 drinks?
What?
He ate like 20 bowls of food,
He ate an unbelievable amount of food.
I guess when you go to a local area, you can eat foods that are unique to that area.
We often ask for food by ourselves,
Like, "What do you want to eat, Ebi-chan?
For example, once at a big concert,
Onigiri (rice ball) shop came to our venue,
He would make onigiri right in front of us,
Like talking with an onigiri,
Yeah, that was great.
Oh, that was great.
Uka was on a spring tour this year,
I got to go around quite a bit,
I asked for takoyaki (octopus dumplings) in Osaka,
I asked him for takoyaki (octopus dumplings) and 551's bento boxes,
I also asked for takoyaki in Osaka and ate some of 551's bento boxes,
In Sendai, I asked for a beef tongue bento,
And if we were in Sendai, we would ask for a beef tongue bento, and that kind of catering.
It's a good way to make a splash, isn't it?
When you go to a live concert in a local area.
I'm sure you'll have a lot of MC's asking, "What did you have for lunch?
It's a must.
It's a must, so it's a must even for the re-releases.
It's pretty important to talk about what you ate.
I want to eat the local food.
I want to eat what I saw there.
How about Okinawa?
We went to Okinawa for dinner,
I ate umi budou for the first time there.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was delicious.It was delicious.
It's delicious. It's a little piece of seaweed.
I don't often eat seafood,
I thought I'd try the sea grapes,
The members were asking for it,
I was like, "Ceresa Moa, Ceresa Moa, one of our members,
Moa-chan bought about six boxes of umi budou as souvenirs,
I think she bought them for her family in Okinawa,
I ate them too, and they were so soft and crunchy.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I thought it was delicious, so I ate it.
I want to go to Okinawa.
I want to change the subject.
Okay, I want to go to Okinawa for a one-on-one.
I want to do it!
Sure, I'd love to.
Please do.
Because we haven't had any two man shows recently.
We haven't done it.
It's like we're meeting at Stuff Fest.
I'd like to meet you.
It's been a while.
We'd like to have a friendly live concert in Okinawa, not a bickering one.
Like a joint school trip.
Yes, I want to do that!
I'd love to have you do that.
So, speaking of catering that gets people excited,
It is local food.
Good, that's good.
Let's wrap it up.
Yes, let's.
Ready.
Speaking of catering that gets people excited,
It is local food.
That's right.
I knew it.That's right.
I would be very happy if we could have something unique to our house.
That's why we had a special talk festival.
We talked a lot.
We talked about many things.
I'm so happy.
I was happy to hear about other catering situations.
It was a pleasure. Thank you.
Yes, so we will send you another dialogue between the two of us tomorrow.
Please look forward to it.
So far, I have been talking with Waka Yasumori of Iginari Tohoku Products,
and Mr. Murahoshi, the director of Ukka.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.